Preliminary Guide to the Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) records, 1867-2006 MS2195
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1974-2006; Series 8
  - People [2007 accretion], 1990-2006; Series 8 Subseries 4
    - Kennan, George, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 245, Folder 15)
    - Kennedy, Edward, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 245, Folder 16)
    - Kinsley, Michael, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 245, Folder 17)
    - Koch, Ed, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 245, Folder 18)
    - Kondracke, Morton, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 245, Folder 19)
    - Kotkin, Joel, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 245, Folder 20)
    - Krikorian, Mark, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 245, Folder 21)
    - People: L, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 245, Folder 22)
    - Lamm, Hon. Richard, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 245, Folder 23)
    - Lamm, Hon. Richard, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 245, Folder 24)
    - Lind, Michael, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - Ling-Ling, Yeh, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - People: M, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - Malkin, Michelle, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - Mann, Charles, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Martin, Jack, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 8)
    - Martin, Philip, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Massey, Douglas [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 6)
    - Massey, Douglas [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 7)
    - Matloff, Norman, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Matloff, Norman, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 255, Folder 5)
    - McNary, Eugene, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Mehlman, Ira, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Meissner, Doris, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Meyer, Cord, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Miles, Jack, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - People: N, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Navarette, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Nelson, Lars-Erik, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Nelson, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Norquist, Grover, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - People: O, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Olvera, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - People: P, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Papademetrious, Demetrios, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Park, Bob, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - People: Q, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - People: R, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Rabb, Harriett, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Rahman, Omar Abel, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Raspberry, William, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Ray, Dave, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Rees, Grover, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - Reno, Janet, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - Rodriguez, Richard, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - Rohrabacher, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - Roosevelt, President Franklin D., undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - Rosenthal, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 21)
    - People: S, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 197, Folder 22)
    - Saunders, Debra J., undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Schuck, Peter, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Seeley, Ben, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Simcox, David, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Simon, Julian, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Simon, Julian, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Simpson, Alan, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Skerry, Peter, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Lamar, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 10)
    - Solarz, Stephen, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 11)
    - Sontag, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 12)
    - Sowell, Thomas, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 246, Folder 13)
    - Stein, Dan, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Sutherland, Daniel, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - People: T, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Tancredo, Tom, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Tanton, John, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - Teitelbaum, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 6)
    - Torres, Art, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - Trjo, Stephen, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 8)
    - People: U, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - Ungar, Sanford, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 10)
    - People: V, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 11)
    - Vialet, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 12)
    - People: W, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 13)
    - Wattenber/Zinmesiter, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 14)
    - Will, George F., undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 15)
    - Wood, Kimba, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 16)
    - Wilson, Pete, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 17)
    - People: XYZ, undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 247, Folder 18)
  - States and cities [1998 accretion], 1977-1984; Series 8 subseries 2
    This subseries contains subjec files for immigration issues in states and cities. Subseries 5 also contains records related to States and immigration. The records in this subseries were donated separately and have not been merged. Both subseries should be searched to ensure thoroughness.
    - Arizona, 1980; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Arizona, 1982; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - California, 1981-1982; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - California, undated; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Chicago, Illinois, 1980-1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Colorado, 1982; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - District of Columbia, 1984; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Florida, 1979-1982; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Florida, 1981-1984; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Georgia, 1981; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Hawaii, 1980; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Idaho, 1981; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Illinois, 1979-1981; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Illinois, 1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Indiana, undated; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Kentucky, 1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Los Angeles, 1981-1982; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Louisiana, 1984; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Maryland, 1981; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Massachusetts, 1977-1982; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Michigan, 1977, 1979-1984; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Minnesota, 1981; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Minnesota, 1982; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - New Mexico, 1982; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - New Mexico, 1982-1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - New York, 1979-1981; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - New York, 1980-1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - North Carolina, 1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Ohio, 1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Oklahoma, 1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Oregon, 1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania, 1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Rhode Island, 1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - San Diego, 1981-1984; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco, 1980-1984; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Texas, 1981; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Texas, 1981-1984; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Virginia, 1982; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Virginia, 1983-1984; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Washington, 1980-1982; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Washington, 1982-1983; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Washington, D.C., 1979-1984; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Wisconsin, 1980; Series 8 subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Federal departments and offices, 1974-1988; Series 8 subseries 3
    This subseries contains subject files related to immigration issues for the Federal departments and offices. These materials date from 1974-1988.
    - Attorney general Benjamin Civiletti, 1980; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Census bureau, 1979-1980; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Congress, undated; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Court of Appeals, undated; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Department of Agriculture, 1981; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Department of Commerce, unknown; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Department of health, education, and welfare, 1979-1981; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Department of housing and urban development, 1981-1982; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Department of justice, 1979-1982; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Department of justice, 1978-1982; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Equal employment opportunity commission, 1980; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1974; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Health and human services, 1981; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - INS, 1979; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - INS, 1980; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - INS, 1981; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - INS, 1981-1983; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - INS, 1981-1983; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - INS, 1983-1986; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - INS, 1984-1985; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - INS CFR parts, unknown; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - INS oversight hearings, 1987 October 21; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Labor department, 1979-1982; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Labor department H-2 wages, 1980; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Office of refugee resettlement, 1980-1981; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Office of US coordinator for refugee affairs, 1980; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - State Department, 1977-1982; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Supreme Court, 1987-1988; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Supreme Court, undated; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 144, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Court of Appeals, undated; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 144, Folder 22)
    - 99th Congress, undated; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - 100th Congress (1/2), undated; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - 100th Congress (2/2), undated; Series 8 subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - States [2007 accretion], 1992-2002; Series 8 Subseries 5
    This subseries has subject files related to immigration issues in various states. Subseries 2 also contains records for States. The records in this subseries were donated separately and have not been merged. Both subseries should be searched to ensure thoroughness.
    - Alabama, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - Alaska, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Arizona [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Arizona [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - Arkansas, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - California, 1992; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - California, 1993; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - California, 1994; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - California, 1995; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - California, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - California, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - California, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - California, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - California, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - California, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - California, 2002; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - Colorado, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - Delaware, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - District of Columbia [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Florida, 1992; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Florida, 1993; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Florida, 1994; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Florida, 1995; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Florida, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Florida, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - Florida, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - Florida, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - Florida, 2002; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - Georgia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - Hawaii, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Idaho, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Illinois, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - Indiana, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - Iowa, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Iowa [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Iowa [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Kansas, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Kentucky, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - Los Angeles, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Louisiana, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Maine, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Maine, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Maryland, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Michigan, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Minnesota [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Mississippi, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 224, Folder 2)
      This folder does not contain any documents. It was empty when donated to the library.
    - Missouri, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - Montana, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - Nebraska, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Nevada, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - New Hampshire, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - New Jersey, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - New Mexico, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 224, Folder 8)
    - New York, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 224, Folder 9)
    - New York City, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - North Carolina, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - North Dakota, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - Ohio, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - Oklahoma, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - Oregon, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - Rhode Island, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - South Carolina, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - South Dakota, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Tennessee, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Texas, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - Utah, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Vermont, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Virginia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - Washington, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - West Virginia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - Wisconsin, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - Wyoming, undated; Series 8 Subseries 5 (Box 219, Folder 12)
  - General subject files, 1980-2003; Series 8 Subseries 6
    This subseries contains subject files maintained by FAIR dealing with topics in immigration. These materials date from Circa 1980 - Circa 2003.
    - 1980 Census, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - 1986 IRCA Amnesty, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - 1990 Census, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - 2000 Census [1/2], Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - 2000 Census [2/2], Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - 2003 Issues: Amnesty, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - 2003 Issues: Guestworker, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - 2003 Issues: H1B, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - 2003 Issues: In-State, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - 2003 Issues: Homeland Security, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - 2003 Issues: Healthcare, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - 2003 Issues: Consular ID, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - 2003 Borders: Open Borders, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - 245(i), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Abortion, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Adjustment of Legal Status, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Adoptees, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Adoption, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Adult Education, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Agricultural Industry [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Industry [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Aid to Families w/ Dependant Children (AFDC), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 190, Folder 1)
      General Note
    - Airports [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Airports [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - American Community Survey (ACS), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - American Identity, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Americanization, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - American Watch, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Amnestied Families, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Amnesties for Illegal Aliens, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Amnesty Fraud, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Amnesty, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Amnesty: Proposals for Amnesty [1/2] undated, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Amnesty: Proposals for Amnesty [2/2] undated, Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Anchor Babies, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Anchor Babies, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Anchor Babies: Benefits, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Anchor Babies: Repeal, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Apprehensions, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Arab Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Asians, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - Assimilation, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Asylee Detention, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Asylum Backlog, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Asylum Bias, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Asylum Cases, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Asylum for Religious Persecution, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Asylum for Women, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Asylum Fraud, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Asylum from Torture, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Asylum Reform, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Asylum Statistics, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Asylum, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Au Pairs, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Backlash Against Immigration Reform, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - Backlash Against Immigration, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - Balkinization, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Bases for Asylum, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Bilingual Education Cases, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Bilingual Education Reform, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Bilingual Education, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Billingual Ballots, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Birth Dearth, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Black Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Black Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Bodyshops (G-132), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - Border Checkpoints, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Border Environment, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Border flow, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Border Militarization, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Border Patrol (The) [1/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Border Patrol (The) [2/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Border Patrol (The) [3/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Border Patrol Abuses [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Border Patrol Abuses [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Border Patrol Funding [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Border Patrol Funding [/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - [Border Security], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 255, Folder 7)
    - [Border Security Conference Packet], dated 2006, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - Border Structures and Mechanisms [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Border Structures and Mechanisms [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 161, Folder 2)